Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Papers of Peter Wexler (1965 - ongoing)
MS 338
Wexler, Peter
Papers and Artwork of Artist, Producer, Director, Scenery Designer, Lighting Designer, and Costume Designer, Peter John Wexler, 1965-. Contains papers, documents, records, drawings, models, photographs, slides, film, and other materials.
328 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are restrictions on access to this collection. Specific equipment to view or listen to some media materials may not be available at the University of Arizona Special Collections Library.
Biographical Sketch
Peter John Wexler was born to S. David and Berda (Sarnoff) Wexler in New York City, 31 October 1936. He married Constance Ann Ross, 30 November 1962. Peter Wexler's early education was in the New York Public School system. In 1958, he received a Bachelor of Science degree in Design from the University of Michigan School of Architecure. That same year he enrolled as a student in the Yale School of Drama. He received early training in scenery painting early in his career at the Cleveland Playhouse in Chautauqua, New York and Chautauqua Opera Association, New York. Mr. Wexler's professional affiliations include the United Scenic Artists, the International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, and the United States Institute of Theatre and Technology.
Mr. Wexler's designs and artworks range from interior design for individual persons to grand scale multimedia events. His works include, but are not limited to, projects for the following theatres and organizations: Center Theatre Group, Los Angeles; New York Philharmonic; Metropolitan Opera; Pittsburgh Public Theatre; Dallas Symphony Orchestra; Smithsonian Institute; Trammell Crow Company; Arizona Theatre Company; Trans-Hudson Ferry, Port Authority of New York and New Jersey; National Symphony Orchestra; and the United States Navy. His creative work extends to genres such as film and television. In these genres, Mr. Wexler has contributed to such films as: Andy, 1965; Happy Time, 1967; Camino Real, 1970; The Trial of the Catonsville Nine, 1973; and Les Troyens, 1973. His television credits include: The Merv Griffin show; Life Med, cable; and the Cleo Awards Ceremony. Mr. Wexler has also lectured and or taught at the University of Michigan, State University of New York and Binghamton, and the University of Arizona.
Awards include: ANTA-ITI "War and Peace" competition award winner, Spring 1965; Drama Desk and Joseph Maharam Awards 1968; Tony (Antoinette Perry) Award nominee 1968; Los Angeles Drama Critics Circle award, 1971 and 1972.
Information for this biographical sketch has been compiled from the collection itself as well as the following publications which have included Peter John Wexler among the notable people in America and in his field:
Biography Index. Vol. 10: September, 1973 - August, 1976. (New York: H. W. Wilson Co., 1977.) Blue Book. Leaders of the English Speaking World. 1976 Edition. (London: St. James Press; New York: St. Martin's Press, 1976. Two volume reprint by Gale Research, Detroit, 1979.) Contemporary Theatre, Film, and Television. vols. 5 and 6. (Detroit: Gale Research, 1988 - 1989.) Metropolitan Opera Encyclopedia. (New York: Simon and Shuster, 1987.) Notable Names in the American Theatre. (Clifton, NJ: James T. White and Co., 1976.) Who's Who in the Theatre. 16th and 17th editions. (London: Pitman Publishing; Detroit: Gale Research, 1977, 1981.) Who's Who in America. 38th and 49th editions. (Wilmette, IL: Marquis Who's Who, 1974, 1995.)
Organization
This collection is organized into 3 series
Series I: Papers.
Series II: Artwork.
Series III: Models.
Folder titles remain as they were given by Peter Wexler, Inc. Ongoing accession of materials from Mr. Wexler's continued professional activity are added to the collection by project and date in the order they are received.
Due to processing constraints, the photographs, slides, and related materials were not separated into their own series and remain in their original files.
Scope and Content Note
The collection documents Peter Wexler's professional activity from 1967 to the present. The materials have been gathered into three series: Papers, Artwork, and Models. The center of the collection is the Artwork series that consists of large, blueprint size, mechanical drawings of floorplans and elevations of scenery for concerts, films, industrial shows, multi-media events, and theatrical productions.
The bulk of the Papers series supports Peter Wexler and Peter Wexler Inc. projects in the Artwork series. The Papers series includes correspondence with clients and vendors, scripts, scores, and cue sheets, research, visual research through photos and photocopies. Correspondences include those with important persons in the field of Opera, Theatre and entertainment. The collection is inclusive of designs and artwork for original productions such as Godspell.
Related Material
Additional materials in the Peter Wexler collection are held in the library of the State University of New York at Binghamton and at New York Public Library. The New York Public Library materials can be viewed online at http://www.nypl.org/research/lpa/the/pdf/THEwexler.pdf http://www.nypl.org/research/lpa/dan/pdf/DANwexler.pdf
Other theatre related materials in the University of Arizona Special Collections include the manuscripts of playwright and novelist Sophie Treadwell, MS 124 and MS318; and Thomas Wood Stevens, MS 2.
Access Terms
Wexler, Peter, 1936-
Set designers.
Costume designers.
Designers -- United States.
Opera -- United States.
Stage lighting designers.
Television -- Stage-setting and scenery.
Theaters -- Stage-setting and scenery.
Container List
- Papers., Series:I
  The series includes photos, and media materials.
  Arrangement: Chronological and then under project. Consult later box listings for projects added to the collection out of sequence.
  Quantity: 137 boxes. 156 linear feet.
  Description: Contains budgets, cassette tapes, contracts, correspondence, cue sheets, exhibition materials, film, memos, photos, playbills, publicity, reviews, samples, scripts, slides, storyboards, and research materials.
  - War and Peace. Photo. 1964 (Box 1)
  - Contract Duplicates. undated (Box 1)
  - The Planets. Gustav Holst. Score. Script. 1967 (Box 1)
  - First Season. Israel Horowitz. Script. 1967 (Box 1)
  - Childhood Set Models. Photos. 1967 (Box 1)
  - The Devils. 1967 (Box 1)
  - Lizzie Borden Revival. 1967 (Box 1)
  - Theatre Crafts magazine. 1967 (Box 1)
  - The Happy Time. Reviews and Publicity. 1968 (Box 1)
  - Antoinette Perry Awards. 1968 (Box 1)
  - Maharam Awards. 1968 (Box 1)
  - Theatre Crafts. On Designing for the New York Philharmonic. 1969 (Box 1)
  - State Department Tour - Reviews and Publicity. 1969 (Box 1)
  - State Department Tour - General. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Prometheus. Reviews and Publicity. 1969 (Box 1)
  - New York State University. Lecture and letters. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Uncle Vanya. Costumes. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Wright, Hepburn, Webster Gallery Show. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Players Magazine. August / September. 1969 (Box 1)
  - The Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer - Film, Corrected. Slides, Corrected. 1969 (Box 1)
  - The Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer - Film, Corrected. Scripts, Corrected. 1969 (Box 1)
  - The Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer - New York. General. 1969 (Box 1)
  - The Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer - New York. Photos. 1969 (Box 1)
  - The Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer - New York. Reviews and Publicity. 1969 (Box 1)
  - The Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer - New York. Notes, letters, etc. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Drama at Calgary. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Chemin De Fer - Script with cues. 1969. (Box 1)
  - Chemin De Fer - Properties. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Chemin De Fer - Reviews and Publicity. 1969 (Box 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Projections Layouts. 1969 (Box 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Slides. 1969 (Box 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Lighting. Daily Schedules. Contracts. Letters. 1969 (Box 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Lighting. Cue Sheets, Console Layouts. 1969 (Box 1)
  - Murderous Angels. Reviews and Publicity. 1970 (Box 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Lighting. 1970 (Box 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Stage Schedules. Lists. Publicity and Reviews. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Reinhardt Symposium. Publicity and Reviews. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Rosebloom - Script. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Rosebloom - Budget. Swatches, etc. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Rosebloom - Reviews and Publicity. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Olympia Theatre Project. Reviews and Publicity. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Minnie's Boys - Later Additions Script. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Minnie's Boys - Second Script. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Minnie's Boys - Reviews and Publicity. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Minnie's Boys - Correspondence, General. 1970 (Box 1)
  - Abraham Lincoln - Scripts. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Abraham Lincoln - Reviews and Publicity. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Abraham Lincoln - Production schedules, letters, notes. 1971 (Box 2)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Lighting magic and cue sheets. 1971 (Box 2)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Reviews and Publicity. 1971 (Box 2)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades - Worksheets, notes. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Cleo Awards - Film Titles. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Cleo Awards - Cue sheets, programs. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Cantonsville Nine. New York. Playbills. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Cantonsville Nine. Los Angeles. Reviews and Publicity. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Arlen Realty. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Brody Corporation. Carts. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Godspell - Reviews and Publicity. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Godspell - General. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Cantonsville Nine - Reviews and Publicity. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Cantonsville Nine - General photos. 1971 (Box 2)
  - The Gershwin Years. Cue Sheets, Publicity, Prod. List. 1971 (Box 2)
  - University of Arizona lecture. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Murderous Angels - Script. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Murderous Angels - Working Script. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Center Theatre Group. 1971 (Box 2)
  - Drama Critics Circle. 1971 (Box 2)
  - George Nash. 1972 (Box 3)
  - The Web and the Rock - Script. 1972 (Box 3)
  - The Web and the Rock - General. 1972 (Box 3)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Lighting cue sheets. 1972 (Box 3)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - General. 1972 (Box 3)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Reviews and Publicity. 1972 (Box 3)
  - The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing 1972 (Box 3)
  - Curlew River. 1972 (Box 3)
  - Lorrie - Script. 1972 (Box 3)
  - Lorrie - General, publicity, photos. 1972 (Box 3)
  - Happy Talk - Script. 1972 (Box 3)
  - Happy Talk - General, publicity, cues. 1972 (Box 3)
  - Appointments and phone diary. undated (Box 3)
  - Mass - Reviews and Publicity. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Mass - General. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Mass - Performance material. 1973 (Box 4)
  - DeGaetani Paper. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Actors Fund Auction. 1973 (Box 4)
  - New York Philharmonic. Hall Seating Platforms. 1973 (Box 4)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Lighting - Magic Sheets, Cue Sheets. 1973 (Box 4)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Reviews and Publicity. 1973 (Box 4)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - General. 1973 (Box 4)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - Lighting. Magic Sheets. Cue Sheets. 1973 (Box 4)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - Reviews and Publicity. 1973 (Box 4)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - General. 3 photos. 1 carpet sample. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Stage B - Reviews and Publicity. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Stage B - General. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Les Troyens - Fabric - 23 Plates, 2 Feathers, 1 Envelope. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Les Troyens - Costumes. Preliminary. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Les Troyens - Costumes. Swatches. Charts. Sketches. 3 folders. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Les Troyens - Score, unbound. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Les Troyens - General. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Britten Triptych - Costumes. Fabric Swatches. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Britten Triptych - Costumes. Fabric and Sketches.. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Britten Triptych - Lighting. Cue Sheets. Cheat Sheets. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Britten Triptych - Reviews and Publicity.. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Britten Triptych - General. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Review of Revues - Reviews and Publicity. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Britten Triptych - General. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Review of Revues - Reviews and Publicity. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Review of Revues - General. 1973 (Box 4)
  - Les Troyens - Reviews and Programs. undated (Box 5)
  - Les Troyens - Reviews and Publicity. Articles. 2 folders. undated (Box 5)
  - Reviews and Publicity. Distribution is... undated (Box 5)
  - Reviews and Publicity. Letters and Telegrams. In 1973 box. undated (Box 5)
  - Film Publicity Photos. 9. 1 and 2. undated (Box 5)
  - Film General. undated (Box 5)
  - Lighting Cue Sheets. undated (Box 5)
  - Scenery. Summaries. Prop List. undated (Box 5)
  - Costume Stock Pulling List. 12 plates of photos. undated (Box 5)
  - Cassette 1. Reel of Film 1. undated (Box 5)
  - Hamlet - Lighting. 3 envelopes. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Hamlet - Reviews and Publicity. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Henry IV - Script. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Henry IV - Revised Script with Cues. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Henry IV - Lighting Final. Hookups and Cue Sheets. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Henry IV - Reviews and Publicity. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Henry IV - General. 1974 (Box 6)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Reviews and Publicity. 1974 (Box 6)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Lighting Magic and Cue Sheets. 1974 (Box 6)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - The Lagoon. Score. Sketches. 1974 (Box 6)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Exhibit "Great Ladies." 1974 (Box 6)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - General. 1974 (Box 6)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - Reviews and Publicity. 1974 (Box 6)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - General. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Museum for the Performing Arts. Exhibit. 1974 (Box 6)
  - University of California at Davis. Gene Chesley 1974 (Box 6)
  - Huntington's Disease Foundation. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Chautauqua Daily. Reviews and Publicity. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Stage Design Throughout the World Since 1960. 1974 (Box 6)
  - International Theatre Institute of the United States. Exhibition. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Hollywood Bowl - General. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Hollywood Bowl - General Development. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Hollywood Bowl - Meeting Summaries. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Hollywood Bowl - Contacts, People. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Hollywood Bowl - Systems Pre-programs. 1974 (Box 6)
  - Hollywood Bowl - Pre-program Notes. Letters. 1974 (Box 7)
  - Hollywood Bowl - Various. 1974 (Box 7)
  - Hollywood Bowl - Systems. 1974 (Box 7)
  - University of California at San Diego. Exhibition. 1975 (Box 7)
  - National Register of Prominent Americans. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Philanthropist - Completed Chicago Script with notes. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Philanthropist - Programs and Publicity. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Philanthropist - Chicago Business. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Philanthropist - General. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Philanthropist - Washington Business. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Restaurant. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Exhibition. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Lighting. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Reviews and Publicity.. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Budget. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - Business. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Promenades - General. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - Lighting. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - Reviews and Publicity. 1975 (Box 7)
  - New York Philharmonic Rug Concerts - General. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Glass Menagerie - Lighting. 3 envelopes. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Glass Menagerie - Costumes. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Glass Menagerie - General. 1975 (Box 7)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest - Lighting. 2 envelopes. 1975 (Box 7)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest - General. 1975 (Box 7)
  - Who's Who in Opera. 1975 (Box 8)
  - Avery Fisher Hall. General. 1975 (Box 8)
  - The Interview. General. 1975 (Box 8)
  - Metropolitan Opera. Auction. 1975 (Box 8)
  - Lynn Pektal Book. 1975 (Box 8)
  - Oenslager Exhibit. 1975 (Box 8)
  - First Reading to First Night. 1975 (Box 8)
  - Touchstone Gallery. 1975 (Box 8)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre. General. 1975 (Box 8)
  - America On Stage. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Tanglewood. General. 1976 (Box 8)
  - RTKL Associates. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Who's Who. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre - Henry V. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre -Phase 2. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre - Seating Phase 2. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Lizzie Borden. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - St. Paul. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Seattle. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - San Diego. 1976 (Box 8)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Israel. Lighting. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Tel Aviv. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Washington, D.C. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - General. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Business. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello -Preliminary Presentation. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Lighting Cue Sheets. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Scenery and Costumes. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Costumes. As Submitted, June 1975. 1975 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Costumes. As Corrected, July 1976. 2 Books. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Houston Grand Opera. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Prompt Book as of Opening. Houston, January 1976. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Prompt Book as of Opening. Washington, March 1976. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Prompt Book as of Opening. Israel, July 1976. With slides. 1976 (Box 9)
  - Fisher Club. Othello - Reviews and Publicity. 1975 (Box 9)
  - Les Troyens - 3 filmstrip canisters. 1973 (Box 10)
  - Les Troyens - 1 audio cassette. 1973 (Box 10)
  - Les Troyens - Reels of film. 1973 (Box 10)
  - Le Prophet - General. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Le Prophet - Reviews and Publicity. 2. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Le Prophet - Costumes. 5. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Le Prophet - Exhibit and Sale. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Hamlet. Arizona Civic Theatre. Script. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Hamlet. Arizona Civic Theatre. Lighting Cues. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Hamlet. Arizona Civic Theatre. Credits. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Jockey's - General. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Jockey's - Costumes. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Jockey's - Reviews and Publicity. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Jockey's - Lighting. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Jockey's - Script. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Avery Fisher Hall. General. 1977 (Box 12)
  - New York Philharmonic. Rug Concerts. Lighting. Rough. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Johnny Mercer Theatre. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association. Auction. Includes 8x10. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Newspaper Coverage. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Who's Who. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Art Institute of Chicago. Includes 8x10s of theatre. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Woman's Day. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Texaco Exhibit. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Treats - Complete Production Book. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Treats - Budget and Reviews. 1977 (Box 12)
  - Who's Who. 1978 (Box 12)
  - A Broadway Musical - General. 1978 (Box 12)
  - A Broadway Musical - Workshop Church. 1978 (Box 12)
  - A Broadway Musical - Technical Information. 1978 (Box 12)
  - A Broadway Musical - Reviews and Publicity. 1978 (Box 12)
  - L'Architecture D'Aujourd'hui. 1978 (Box 12)
  - M. Ruttenberg Article. Interview of Wexler. 1978 (Box 12)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream. 1978 (Box 12)
  - Opera Guild. 1978 (Box 13)
  - By Strouse - General. 1978 (Box 13)
  - By Strouse -Reviews and Publicity. 1978 (Box 13)
  - By Strouse - Production Book. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Pace University Show. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Cooper Hewitt. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Chautauqua Daily. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Aquarius Theatre. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Early Study Summer. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Early Study Spring. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Cold Storage - General. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Cold Storage -Early Scripts. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Cold Storage - Script with Cues. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Cold Storage - Physical Information. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Cold Storage - Reviews and Publicity. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Rip Torn. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Avery Fisher Hall. Reviews and Publicity. 1978 (Box 13)
  - Avery Fisher Hall - Technical Information. 1978 (Box 14)
  - Avery Fisher Hall. Revisions. Promenades and Rug Concerts. 1978 (Box 14)
  - Vojtech Blau Gallery. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Vojtech Blau Gallery. 1979 (Box 14)
  - New York Cultural Amusement Center. 1979 (Box 14)
  - American Academy of Dramatic Arts. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Warren Robertson Studio. "Trilby". 1979 (Box 14)
  - Fushion Ballet. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Israel Park. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Powell Bohlen. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Prophete Revival. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Royal Hunt of the Sun. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Who's Who. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Berda Wexler Apartment. 1979 (Box 14)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Duplicate Presentation Books. 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Consultants. undated (Box 14)
  - Metropolitan Opera - Ballo en Maschera, Tempest in a Tea Pot. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Metropolitan Opera - Ballo en Maschera. 8x10s and notes. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Metropolitan Opera - Ballo en Maschera. 2 folders. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre Death of a Salesman. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre - Reviews and Publicity. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Citicorp. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Chautauqua. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Who's Who. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Drama Logue. 1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Memoranda. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - New Hall. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Photographs. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Original Presentation Books. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Vendors I. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Vendors II. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Temporary Performance Facility. Vendors III. Empty file. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Starfest. Slide Index. Note inside indicates that the file is at Wexler's. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - TV. 2 folders. 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - TV. 3 of 4. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Vendors II. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Vendors III. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Interim report. Summary. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Starfest 1980. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Memoranda. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Budget and Contract. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Programs and Contracts. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Previous year references. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Graphics. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Public Relations. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Publicity and Reviews. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Facilities. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Sound. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Lighting Vendors. 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest - Lighting. 1 of 4. 1980 (Box 16)